<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Getting Started on WiseHub MG | Digital Clouds</title>
    <link>https://ss-o.github.io/series/getting-started/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Getting Started on WiseHub MG | Digital Clouds</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://ss-o.github.io/series/getting-started/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>(Hu)go Template Primer</title>
      <link>https://ss-o.github.io/posts/hugo-template-primer/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ss-o.github.io/posts/hugo-template-primer/</guid>
      <description>Hugo uses the excellent go html/template library for its template engine. It is an extremely lightweight engine that provides a very small amount of logic. In our experience that it is just the right amount of logic to be able to create a good static website. If you have used other template systems from different languages or frameworks you will find a lot of similarities in go templates.
This document is a brief primer on using go templates.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Started with Hugo</title>
      <link>https://ss-o.github.io/posts/hugoisforlovers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ss-o.github.io/posts/hugoisforlovers/</guid>
      <description>Step 1. Install Hugo Goto hugo releases and download the appropriate version for your os and architecture.
Save it somewhere specific as we will be using it in the next step.
More complete instructions are available at installing hugo
Step 2. Build the Docs Hugo has its own example site which happens to also be the documentation site you are reading right now.
Follow the following steps:
 Clone the hugo repository Go into the repo Run hugo in server mode and build the docs Open your browser to http://localhost:1313  Corresponding pseudo commands:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Migrate to Hugo from Jekyll</title>
      <link>https://ss-o.github.io/posts/migrate-from-jekyll/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ss-o.github.io/posts/migrate-from-jekyll/</guid>
      <description>Table of Contents  Move static content to static Create your Hugo configuration file Set your configuration publish folder to site Convert Jekyll templates to Hugo templates Convert Jekyll plugins to Hugo shortcodes  Implementation Usage   Finishing Touches  Fix Content Clean Up   A practical example in a diff  Move static content to static Jekyll has a rule that any directory not starting with _ will be copied as-is to the _site output.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>